<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>Glitter Tech</name>
    <author>Xavior</author>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.0</li>
        <li>1.1</li>
        <li>1.2</li>
        <li>1.3</li>
        <li>1.4</li>
        <li>1.5</li>
    </supportedVersions>
    <modDependencies>
        <li>
            <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
            <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
            <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
        </li>
    </modDependencies>
    <packageId>Xavior.GlitterTech</packageId>
    <description>
        GlitterTech adds a ton of shiny new and futuristic items found on the richer developed Glitter worlds. But, this expensive and illegal tech attracts attention of Glitter world Commandos.

        (Unofficial Version for 1.5 and below)
        *I am not the original author*
        Original Mod: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=725576127
        Pulled and updated from: 725576127 mod folder
        Original Git Repo: https://github.com/sam23694/GlitterTech/tree/1.0.2059
        Current Mod Repo: https://github.com/mdrain18/XaviorsGlitterTech.git

        Updating Mod:
        
        It can be said this mod is OP. I think it should be, however, in the spirit of being able to play how you want to I am adding a few changes to this mod.

        Currently: Working on getting this CE compatible but I need help with testing to see what needs to be patched
        1) Add some Anomaly specific items... ideas are welcome :)
        2) Glitter tech incidents and quests
            - Archotech quest: three abandon glitter tech outposts which have consoles that need to be decrypted. Each gives you 1/3 of the location, collect all three and you will get the location of the archotech factory, which is hidden deep into a side of a mountain. Once there, there will be several boxes with archotech prosthetics, psylinks (if you have the DLC), Archite capsules (if you have the DLC),  
        3) Glitter Tech Weapons and Armor Expanded
        4) Craft Glitter Tech Weapons and Armor Expanded:
            - I'm thinking of adding special items which can only be found via quests
        5) More..... STUFF! Starting with Glitter swords and Glitter psycasts... I think. Not sure if I will ever get
        here but I'm being optimistic

        Let me know in the "Changes" discussion what you want done with this mod and I will do my best to make it
        happen. Link below:
        https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/discussion/2558099206/3480742287613877229/

        Release Notes: 1.5.40602
        - Updated to work with release
        - Added Resource Slider - this will change the stat values of the three resources of this mod based on what the slider is set to
        - Added Titanium yield setting slider
        - Added three army incident where Commandos and OC's fight the Empire!
            (includes settings for changing various parts of the incident)

        
        Release Notes: 1.4.04
        - Titanium is now Titanium_GT which should fix problems with other metal mods that have titanium in them
        - Updated to 1.4: Except:
        - Tanks: big problems here which I am tabling for now
        not sure why this isn't working
        - Tanks have been completely removed and should not spawn so the error shouldn't happen
    </description>
</ModMetaData>